{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "Question": "How much of the ocean have we explored in total?",
            "Answers": ["1%", "5%", "10%", "50%"],
            "Key": "B",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the deepest trench in the sea?",
            "Answers": ["Marina Trench", "Mariana Trench", "Sierena deep", "Marinara Trench"],
            "Key": "B",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "The technology that allows submarines to detect objects is?",
            "Answers": ["Sonar", "Radar", "Gamma", "Ultraviolet"],
            "Key": "A",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the saltiest body of water?",
            "Answers": ["Don Juan Pond", "Alantic Ocean", "Dead Sea", "Great Salt Lake"],
            "Key": "A",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What war were submarines first used?",
            "Answers": ["World War I", "World War II", "Civil War", "The Napoleonic Wars"],
            "Key": "C",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the name of the deepest underwater cave explored by man?",
            "Answers": ["Krubera-Voronja cave", "Sarma cave", "Hranicka Propast cave", "Abisso Paolo Roversi cave "],
            "Key": "C",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What type of rock is most commonly associated with cave formations?",
            "Answers": ["Granite", "Basalt", "Olivine", "Limestone"],
            "Key": "D",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What fish goes through decompression sickness when brought out of their habitat?",
            "Answers": ["Pufferfish", "Oarfish", "Swordfish", "Blobfish"],
            "Key": "D",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What property makes certain marine life glow?",
            "Answers": ["Refraction", "Bioluminescence", "Radiance", "Radiation"],
            "Key": "B",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "How many species of sharks are there?",
            "Answers": ["100", "50", "500", "63"],
            "Key": "C",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "what is the scientific name for a giant squid?",
            "Answers": ["Architeuthidae", "Cephalopoda", "Megaloteuthis", "Architeuthus"],
            "Key": "A",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "How much of the ocean have we explored in total?",
            "Answers": ["1%", "5%", "10%", "50%"],
            "Key": "B",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the deepest trench in the sea?",
            "Answers": ["Marina Trench", "Mariana Trench", "Sierena deep", "Marinara Trench"],
            "Key": "B",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "The technology that allows submarines to detect objects is?",
            "Answers": ["Sonar", "Radar", "Gamma", "Ultraviolet"],
            "Key": "A",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the saltiest body of water?",
            "Answers": ["Don Juan Pond", "Alantic Ocean", "Dead Sea", "Great Salt Lake"],
            "Key": "A",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What war were submarines first used?",
            "Answers": ["World War I", "World War II", "Civil War", "The Napoleonic Wars"],
            "Key": "C",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the name of the deepest underwater cave explored by man?",
            "Answers": ["Krubera-Voronja cave", "Sarma cave", "Hranicka Propast cave", "Abisso Paolo Roversi cave "],
            "Key": "C",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What type of rock is most commonly associated with cave formations?",
            "Answers": ["Granite", "Basalt", "Olivine", "Limestone"],
            "Key": "D",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What fish goes through decompression sickness when brought out of their habitat?",
            "Answers": ["Pufferfish", "Oarfish", "Swordfish", "Blobfish"],
            "Key": "D",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "What property makes certain marine life glow?",
            "Answers": ["Refraction", "Bioluminescence", "Radiance", "Radiation"],
            "Key": "B",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "How many species of sharks are there?",
            "Answers": ["100", "50", "500", "63"],
            "Key": "C",
            "Hint": ""
        },
        {
            "Question": "what is the scientific name for a giant squid?",
            "Answers": ["Architeuthidae", "Cephalopoda", "Megaloteuthis", "Architeuthus"],
            "Key": "A",
            "Hint": ""
        }

    ]
}